This is our turn! Yeah!
If any of those pirates tries to
set foot on these grounds tonight,
it'll be the last thing they do!
The honor of Galilee law depends on it!
Is the back door covered?
Yeah, we got guys covering the entire
perimeter of this place and then some!
Nobody's getting in here!
Come on, pirates!
I dare ya!
Bring it on! Yeah!
They're all huge and armed and angry.
We need to be careful.
Those guys have a
reputation for being able
to handle themselves
when push comes to shove.
We don't want to rush in and do
anything we're going to regret later.
Yeah, if we try to barge in swinging,
we'll just be asking for trouble.
Right.
And we wouldn't want any trouble, says
the guy who charged in in broad daylight.
Anyway, don't take your
eyes off him, Chopper.
We don't want any kind of
surprise down there. Right.
Anything happens, you let us know.
Okay, you got it.
I think we're going to have a
really long night ahead of us.
But if we blow our opportunity, it's over.
We can't let our guard down
no matter what happens.
If we want to know the truth about Robin,
then it has to be tonight or never.
Yeah, I got a feeling we'll
be talking to her real soon.
We'll
see
you next time.
Kali-Fa?
Yes, Mr. Iceberg?
Not to be rude, but do you mind
stepping out of the room for a moment?
No, of course not.
One more thing.
Fetch Polly.
I need to have a word with him.
Excuse me, Polly. Huh? Mr.
Iceberg needs to see you.
I assume it's very important.
He asked for me?
Yes, specifically.
I have some things to take care of
in my office if anyone needs me.
Right.
Seems like awfully strange timing
for a one-on-one conversation.
What in blazes could it be about?
Don't have a clue.
It's his will!
Well, what are you doing out here?
Go on in there and talk to him.
Uh, sure.
Don't worry, we can step away from the
door if you're concerned about privacy.
Good idea.
What the heck could he want
to talk about with Polly?
Whatever it is, it's between them.
We got enough to deal with.
I think we need to stay
focused on our pirate problem.
Right.
Okay, according to Kalifa, it's a small
group with only seven people on their crew.
Who wants to watch out for us?
Straw Hat Luffy, Pirate
Hunter Zoro, and Nico Robin.
I wouldn't underestimate the
girl traveling along with them,
or that other guy with
the long, round nose.
Yeah.
There are those two you just
mentioned, along with two others.
Cuckoo!
It doesn't matter what
those pirates are after.
They set foot on this property
tonight, they're done for.
Every single last one of them. Got it?
Cuckoo!
Right!
Yeah, I understand, sir.
I apologize for putting you in
harm's way like this, Polly.
But this is a very grave matter,
and I trust you can get it done.
Can I put my faith in you?
I give you my word, sir.
I swear, I won't let you down.
You're a good man.
Well, suppose I should
get on it. Thank you.
Cuckoo!
I'm talking with you!
Yeah.
Hey, listen, guys.
I gotta head out and take care of something.
Cool? No problem. That'll be fine.
The four of us will keep
watch over things here.
Thanks.
Just keep Iceberg's safe, you guys.
When you leave here, go straight
to my office and move my desk.
I want you to lift up the
rug and look underneath it.
There's a safe hidden there.
Jackpot.
Once you find that,
enter this combination.
First, right to number six.
are you ready yes awaiting
your signal it will be very
soon now at that time the four
of you are to carry out your
respective missions with ruthless
efficiency as a loyal member
of Cape you have my word nico
robin are you ready yes i am
Whoa!
Something blew up!
Oh no!
What the hell was that?
Grab water now!
We got a man down over here!
Make sure that fire doesn't
spread to the building!
Guys, they're shooting at us! No, man.
I'm pretty sure it was some kind of bomb.
Someone must have said it then.
Hurry, men!
We gotta put out this fire!
Someone give me a hand!
Not too subtle, but it'll do.
Let's move.
The fire's in the north
corner of the first floor.
Has anyone heard?
There have been no pirates spotted yet!
Everyone keep your eyes
peeled for intruders!
Stay at your posts, men!
Don't let them get inside!
Ah!
Iceberg, are you okay?
Yeah, just a bit shocked.
There they are!
It's that guy in the costume! Get him!
Those bastards!
All pounding their faces!
I got your back!
Wait, hold on!
For Pete's sake.
There he goes! Hurry!
We got this clown!
He's alone!
Locks him in!
Stop!
It's the end of the line!
He's heading for the roof!
So you thought you could
get away didn't you punk?
It's gonna take a lot more
than that to get by us!
You made a big mistake when you
decided to mess with Galley-La?
Prepare for the beating of your life!
We're not gonna show any mercy, scumbag!
You can come at me with all
you've got, but it still won't be
Enough?
You
have
the
floor plan
memorized is that correct?
Yes
They all seem pretty worked up down there.
Yeah.
There's definitely something
going on right now.
All right, then.
When are we going to make our move?
Hey, where's Luffy? No!
That idiot!
What about the plan?
I thought we weren't going
to rush into anything!
Too late.
They're going to the back door.
Let's head them off!
No matter what, they can't get inside.
You got a lot of nerve coming here!
After the crap you tried
to pull last night!
You're gonna pay for what you did.
Oh yeah!
You guys are in for a world of hurt.
For messing with Mr.
Iceberg Surrender.
Give it up now!
and we might just go easy on you.
You're surrounded.
There's nowhere to run.
We already know it's not just the two
of you guys and your little pirate gang.
Now, where are the others?
He's pulling out a weapon!
Shoot him!
No way! They're gone?
What the hell?
Where'd they go?
Hey, are you okay?
Man, that guy's a monster.
He flew.
He was flying through the air.
What the hell?
He can fly?
Idiots.
Do you not know when to give up?
He's jumping!
Moonwalk!
What the?
He's really flying!
Thorny Road!
I told you you were bested, didn't I?
Get ready! Here he comes!
He's gonna land in the courtyard!
Don't let him escape!
There he goes!
Get around him!
We can trap him in there!
Yeah!
This is it.
Interesting.
All this time, it was literally
right under our noses.
Hand it over.
You can't possibly
understand its importance.
Who are you bastards?
Where in the hell did you come from?
From the shadows.
Yes, from the darkest
corners of existence.
We bring with us the light of justice.
We are Cipher pole number nine,
an undercover intelligence agency.
Well, no matter where
you freaks came from!
You sure as hell didn't get in without
running into the galley log craftsman.
Perhaps we did.
The details are all very hazy.
A sea of fists and bodies.
What's important is we're here now.
I get it.
This ain't just some
assassination plot, is it?
Very astute but then we never claimed
that it was now did we in any case we
need what iceberg was trying to keep
hidden the item you hold in your trembling
hand now and since you've been made aware
of its existence we need to take your
life as well entrusting you to this task
iceberg has signed your Death warrant.
What's the word?
Did you find him?
Nuh-uh.
There's no sign of those guys anywhere.
They get inside?
There's men standing guard at
every single point of entry.
No, there's no way they got in.
Damn it!
Where the hell did they go?
They couldn't have gotten far.
They've got to be hiding somewhere.
Search the perimeter one more time.
Got it? Yeah!
Here, he's behind this wall.
Right.
Now, give me a push.
Incredible.
I had a feeling you'd
be coming back for me.
But I can't believe my eyes.
Is this how you came in last night?
How is that even possible?
It's the power of the Dordor fruit.
Where a normal man sees a wall,
I see a prospective entryway.
No matter how thick it may be, I
simply touch it and it opens for me.
Hold on.
It's not time yet. Relax.
It's not a fatal wound.
He'll still be able to talk.
I'm just giving him a
taste of what's to come.
Like an appetizer of pain.
What's more, after that,
I don't think he'll be
running off anywhere
before we get the signal
to finish the job.
Or perhaps I should say, to
serve him the main course. I see.
So that's how CP9 handles things, huh?
As a matter of fact, that is how we do it.
That poor straw, boy.
Well, he had nothing to
do with this, did he?
There's no need to beat
yourself up about it.
After all, you simply told the
truth exactly as you saw it,
and I was indeed here last night.
That was all part of your
plan, wasn't it? Right again.
You're alive for two reasons.
First, so you could tell your
story of the failed assassination,
placing a member of the Straw Hat
crew at the scene of the crime.
Secondly, we were trying to
ferret out an important document.
The blueprints of a certain ship.
One that has been passed
down in secret from
shipwright to chosen
apprentice for generations.
We knew that with your
life clearly in danger,
you would pass that document on to
someone you trusted to keep it safe.
You made that choice earlier tonight.
Your foreman, Paulie.
Our associates are with
him this very moment.
It's all going as planned, isn't it?
You must be very damn proud of yourself.
I want you to see this to its end.
Of course, I'll go deal with the
riffraff standing guard outside the door.
When the blueprints are secured, our
associates will contact you at that time.
You will have full clearance
to dispose of iceberg.
Do so at once.
Make sure he dies without fail.
After that, the only remaining
loose end will be Polly.
He dies, and the truth of what's
happened here dies with him.
The blame will remain on the Straw
Hats, and no one's the wiser.
I know he doesn't listen to me.
It's crazy, but I thought maybe
he'd listen to his own advice.
We are talking about Luffy.
Hey, guys,
do you think that's Robin in the middle
of all that commotion down at Galley Law?
No matter what Luffy decided to
do, we still gotta be careful.
Yeah, I know.
But him rushing in like that
might actually work in our favor.
If you think about the way he does things,
is he the kind of guy that's gonna go
in through the back or side entrance?
Not his style. No way. So,
I'm pretty sure by now he's made a go at
barging straight through the front door.
And it's safe to assume that
right now he's running around
inside like crazy because he
has no idea where he's going,
don't you think?
Oh, yeah.
Sounds like him.
Uh-huh.
And from the shipwright's point of view,
he's the leader of the
group that attacked Iceberg.
So if you made it in there by now,
all of those guys are going to
be busy trying to catch him.
Which would mean the guards have
severely thinned out at the front door.
Or at the very least, they're
completely distracted.
So the safest way in right
now is through the front,
right behind all the
chaos in Luffy's wake.
So when he does it,
it's completely stupid.
But if we do the same exact thing,
it's actually a brilliant plan, huh?
Yeah, makes sense.
I say that we should go for it, then.
The gate is right up ahead.
Okay, ready?
It's showtime!
Here we go!
This was a dumb idea!
Crap, this sucks.
I wanted to jump right through
the front door like a typhoon.
But I'm totally stuck.
Gotta get out.
Gotta get Robin.
Oh, what the hell is going on?
We need help on the third floor!
Somebody come to the presence room quick!
The guards are wiped out!
I need backup!
What do you mean wiped out?
Tilestone!
Kokoro and Luchi should be there!
Well, come see!
What?
No way!
Still no word.
I'm getting tired of dealing
with all these idiots.
How dare you!
I'll kill you, bastard!
You're a noisy one, aren't you?
If you lay a single finger on Mr.
Iceberg, I'll tear you limb from limb!
I'd like to see you try...
Iron Body.
Push that giant hammer!
That's not good.
You!
Get your hands off me! Hmph.
Are those muscles just for show?
I can't move my arm!
How is this guy stronger than me?
Oh, he's taken out three
foremen, all on his own.
Peak Rain Force must not stand! Shave.
We found them!
It's Roro, Noah, and Zoro!
They finally showed up!
Don't let them get away!
That woman is one of them two!
If Luffy isn't here, then where is he?
I don't know, why are you asking me?
What now?
Well, they've already found us, so
there's no point in trying to be sneaky.
The only thing left to do
now is go on the offensive.
Wait, what do you think you're doing?
Running circles around the
building won't do us any good.
If we want to find Robin, then we're
going to have to force our way through.
Huh?
Yeah, but those are just shipwrights.
They're not the bad guys.
Then I'll use the back of my swords.
Huh?
If you want to fight, you get it!
You can still kill people
like that, you know!
No!
Well, what a surprise.
After all this time, I never
thought we'd be meeting here,
Nico Robin.
Am I supposed to know you?
Last night was the first time we met.
But for a long time,
I've wanted to see you.
I even put your wanted poster up
in my room so I'd never forget.
Shall I give you an autograph then?
If you sign it. In blood.
You wanted to kill me? That's right.
Before you destroy the world.
Tell me, why are you
looking for the Poneglyphs?
You must know the risk.
For as long as anyone can remember,
the world government has made it
a serious crime to research them.
Why is that knowledge so important?
If they're so bad, then
why do you know about them?
Knowing that the Poneglyphs
exist is hardly a crime.
But deciphering them is another matter.
And you're the only person in
the world who's capable of that.
That's why the world government put
such a large bounty on your head?
Even though you were only
eight years old at the time.
They fear what you're capable of.
Because you alone have the power.
To revive the ancient weapons.
So, you already know?
Yes, but.
I never would have thought
that CP9 was actually real!
And if that's the case,
that means you've already
left the Straw Hats
and you're helping the
world government now.
A strange choice for a woman who's been
on their most wanted list for 20 years.
But, well, I suppose
that's not my concern.
If you decipher the Poneglyphs
and rebuild one of the weapons,
it doesn't matter if the person
who uses it's good or evil.
It's all the same in the end.
A weapon can never be used
to bring peace to this world.
All it can bring is destruction.
We've buried the evils of the past.
Now let them lie.
You may be right, and I don't disagree.
But you don't know why I'm doing this.
You have no right to tell me what I'm
allowed to do or not do with my research,
or what knowledge I can or cannot learn.
Well, I see what you mean.
But the truth is, we might have
more in common than you think.
Perhaps you didn't know.
But I possess the blueprints for
the ancient weapon known as Pluton.
Then they still exist?
Pluton is the name of a battleship built
on this island many years in the past.
The shipwrights who
created the weapon passed
on the blueprints as a
sort of insurance policy.
They feared that another
battleship of equal power would
be necessary if Pluton ever
fell into the wrong hands.
Thankfully, the ship was lost to
history before that could happen.
And now,
the government wants to
revive that power when
there's no force strong
enough to oppose it.
A part of me hopes that you didn't know
that when you agreed to help them out,
but that really doesn't matter now.
A man named Tom entrusted
those blueprints to me,
and he also told me about
a young girl who was the
sole survivor of the Ohara
incident 20 years ago.
He said despite her age,
she was still dangerous because she had
the same ideology as the devils from Ohara.
In honor of Tom and the other shipwrights,
it's my responsibility to stop you.
Of course, now that the government
knows that the blueprints exist,
the logical solution would be to
burn them and be done with this mess.
But I can't do that because
as long as you're alive,
there's a chance that the
weapon could be refilled.
Is that all you want to
say before you die oh?
And with all due respect, even if you had
killed me, nothing would have changed.
The government doesn't need me
to steal the blueprints from you.
I'm sure they've already
accomplished that anyway.
Well, let's not get
ahead of ourselves here.
You're the ones who've fallen for my trap.
Oh, that's it!
I thought I'd never get out of there.
Man, that was terrible.
Okay, let's get it right this time.
I'll find Robin for sure. Gomp!
Gomp!
Rocket!
I'm afraid you're no match
for our martial arts.
Now stop resisting and hand us the document
before you soil it with your blood.
Damn it.
I really thought.
I could beat him.
I should have known better.
This was all my idea.
Iceberg didn't tell me to fight.
He told me to get the hell out of here.
To run.
and leave the blueprints behind.
You know why?
Because those are nothing
but fakes. What? What?
He can't be serious.
What a waste of time.
I don't know who you are, but this
means your plan's a bust, huh?
Too bad.
Sucks to be you.
The funny thing is,
I don't even know what you bastards
were looking for in the first place.
If you think you've
outwitted CP9, you're wrong.
You're merely delaying the inevitable.
At any rate, even though
you're only a decoy,
now that you know the truth,
we can't let you live.
Damn it!
I got stuck again!
Stupid walls always getting in my way!
I hate them!
Why does this always happen to me?
Straw Hat.
Hey, it's the rope guy!
What's going on in here?
Whoa, are you okay?
You're covered in blood.
You sure did surprise me!
Look who's talking.
At least I'm not crashing through walls.
Straw Hat Luffy, how kind of you to
come here to take blame for the crime.
Oh, I get it!
You guys in the masks
must be the ones that
are forcing Robin to
do all this bad stuff,
huh?
You give her back, you bastards!
If I wasn't stuck right now, you'd
be in big trouble! Tempest kick.
He cut right through the wall!
Hey! Behind you!
What are these?
This is an emergency situation.
We don't have time to deal with you.
I can't move.
Restrain Polly, too.
She's given us enough trouble already.
Right.
It's me.
We've hit a snag in the plan.
Everyone head to the bedroom immediately.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
You understand?
I absolutely need him alive.
This has been a delight but I'm
afraid our time is up you see I
have a pressing matter to attend
to running away are you not at all
I'm just finishing you quickly that's all
She's flying!
Hey, you all right?
Are you kidding?
This is nothing.
That's good, I guess.
But why'd you come here
in the first place?
Everyone still thinks you're
the ones who attacked Iceberg.
Sorry about that, by the way.
I realize I might have
jumped the gun a little.
No big deal.
We are pirates, after all.
Anyway, the point is those weird guys
in the masks took one of our crew.
So we're here to get her back.
Nico Robin.
So, you're good at fighting, aren't you?
Hell yeah.
Then you can beat those
guys, huh? You bet.
Good.
We can do this thing together.
Because I'm ready to fight.
Yeah?
Of course I am.
I mean, you think I'm just going to let
some weirdos waltz in out of nowhere,
kick my ass, and then kill Iceberg?
Not a chance!
Who do these punks think they are anyway?
To hell with all this secret agent crap!
Iceberg is...
He's more than just my boss.
He's my teacher.
He made me a shipwright.
I can't let him die! Look
at you. You're a mess.
I told you, I'm ready to fight those
bastards, and I'm not giving up!
I don't care what happens to me,
as long as I can save Iceberg!
Ah, but I can't even move
because I'm stuck to the floor.
This sucks!
Yeah, I know!
Ah!
Go home.
I have nothing to give you people.
Then we have a problem! Don't we?
What does one say to a man
who's marked for death?
First let me be frank.
You disappoint me.
Luchi!
This is your own fault.
You should have handed over the blueprints
when the government asked nicely.
Kaku!
Pity.
I was hoping we could walk away from
this story without resorting to violence.
Kalifa!
It's a shame you're as
hard-headed as your master.
Bruno, from the bar.
That means you've been with
the government all this time.
Indeed.
Needless to say, going undercover
was like second nature to us.
Now, since everyone's being so honest
with each other, let's try this again.
I don't have time to play games.
Tell me, before someone
else gets hurt, where is it?
Where are the blueprints for
the ancient weapon Pluton?